http://www.fanconi.org/explore/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy policy
The Fanconi Anemia Research Fund (FARF) respects the privacy of each individual who uses our website. To safeguard your privacy, we have adopted the following privacy policy. Click here to view our donor and fundraising policies, approved by resolution of the Board of Directors, 7-15-2013.
Normal website usage
The Fund has a strong commitment to Internet privacy. You can visit all portions of our site without revealing your identity or any personal information.
Collection of personally identifiable information
The Fanconi Anemia Research Fund may collect e-mail addresses and other personally identifiable data about visitors when such data is voluntarily submitted to our site. For example, our site may use information collection forms for visitors to request information or to register for the FA Annual Family Meeting or a particular conference. All such information is collected and stored in a manner appropriate to the nature of the data.
Confidentiality of User Information
The Fanconi Anemia Research Fund does not sell, exchange or otherwise disclose user information outside the organization.
Cookies
Like most websites, the Fanconi Anemia Research Fund may place a cookie, or small file, in the browser files of a visitor’s computer. We do not use cookies to track your movement among different web sites and do not exchange cookies with other entities.
Links to Other Sites
Our site provides links to other web sites of relevance to Fanconi anemia. The Fanconi Anemia Research Fund is not responsible for the actions of linked sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of each site you visit.
Privacy Policy Changes
We will post any changes to our privacy policy on this website.
Questions or Concerns
If you have questions about our website privacy practices, feel free to contact us at .(JavaScript must be enabled to view this email address).
Donor Confidentiality Policy
